GREG SITHOLE

I N T E R M E D I A T E F U L L - S T A C K D E V E L O P E R

GET IN TOUCH

Address: 44 Sneddon Street, Sydenham, Johannesburg, 2192 Phone: +27 83 757 7570 Email: gregsithole@hotmail.co.za Website: https://gregsithole@hotmail.co.za

WORK REFERENCES

Deepak Reddy Narahare Senior Web Developer, BMW deepak.narahare@gmail.com +27 61 176 8403

Thapelo Kekana Frontend Developer, FNB thapelosimon@gmail.com +27 65 832 0673

PERSONAL BACKGROUND

My name is Greg Sithole and I'm a Junior Software Developer with several years industry experience. I have great enthusiasm for my work and I believe that it is an important part of my personal growth. In my spare time, I enjoy working on small projects with friends that I have made together. Learning new languages is another passion of mine. In my free time I like to read books and play video games

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Junior Software Developer

Entrostat | May 2017 to present

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained business management & lead integration systems with a small team
- Improved and optimized company's website for seamless customer experience
- Created, communicated, and managed project plans & project timelines
- Worked to continually meet the expectation of our clients

Junior Software Developer

Empire State | Feburary 2016 to May 2017

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications and mobile applications.
- Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.

Software Development Intern

The Digital Academy | December 2015 to Feburary 2016

- Served as a dedicated and supportive Intern in a fast-paced environment.
- Worked to solve complex problems using the latest in Mobile and Web Technologies.

IT Support Assistant

Varsity College Sandton | Feburary 2015 to May 2015

- Worked to support the senior support staff with day-to-day tasks.
- Assisted with the evaluation and troubleshooting of hardware and software issues.
- Maintaining computer Inventory & surplus equipment.

Student Ambassador

Varsity College Sandton | December 2014 to Feburary 2015

- Monitored registration for all prospective student
- Assisted parents and prospective student with necessary registration details.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Varsity College Sandton

IIE Diploma in Information Technology in Software Development Graduated December 2015

- Graduated with Cum laude

Summit College

National Seniors Certificate Graduated December 2012

SKILLS HISTORY

Skills

- **Programming Languages**: JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, HTML, CSS3/SCSS/LESS, PHP
- **Libraries & Frameworks**: jQuery, Angular, Ionic, Vue, Node.js, Express, Nest.js, Sails.js, Laravel
- Tools & Platforms: Git, Wordpress, Docker, Firebase, Digital Ocean, Google Cloud